剧情回顾
Previously on Lost
你想做什么?
- What do you want from me ?
耐心点  Jack  耐心
- Patience, Jack. Patience.
- Danny  等等 - 呆在这
- Danny, wait.  - Hold up.
去那要小心
Be careful out there.
- 看见这些石头了吗? - 你来把它们挖松
See these rocks here? You're gonna chop 'em loose,
你就负责把它们拉走
and you're gonna haul 'em outta here.
我不是你们的敌人
I am not the enemy.
我们都不是敌人
We are not the enemy.
但如果你开枪了
If you shoot me...
那我们就肯定是敌人了
that's exactly what we'll become.
你的...
You've...
你的顶棚有问题
You've got a problem with your roof.
什么?
What ?
也许你今晚可以在海滩上过夜
Maybe you should move on the beach, just for the night.
这样我就可以修一下顶棚了  做一些改进
Then I can fix it and, make some improvments.
非常感谢你的提议
That is really nice of you to offer but,
但是...Aaron刚刚睡着
Aaron just fell asleep,
所以我可能只有...
so I should probably just...
这么做很有必要  相信我
I'll deal with it. I promise.
你在干什么  伙计?
What are you doing, brother ?
我想帮她修理下顶棚
I was just offering to fix this roof here.
顶棚?  好吧
Roof ? Fine.
如果有问题的话我来修好了
If there a problem, i'll fix it.
我比较擅长
I'm quite handy.
在Eko被炸飞前我还在造教堂呢
I was building a church before...Eko explode it.
好吧  那么...
Right, well...
我只是想帮帮你
Just trying to help.
谢谢
Thanks.
到底是怎么回事?
What was all that about ?
不知道
I don't know.
也许我们得另找一个按键让他按
We gonna have together another button push.
今天过得怎样  Jack?
How are you doing today, Jack ?
好极了
Great.
你看起来很沮丧
You seem frustrated.
我是继续看卡通呢
to keep watching cartoons, or...
还是你告诉我为什么我会在这?
are you gonna tell me why I'm here.
我希望你喜欢蓝莓  不喜欢的话我...
I hope you like blueberry. - If not I can...
- 我可以和Benjamin谈谈吗? - 什么?
-Should I talk to Benjamin ?
我可以和Benjamin谈谈吗? 因为我在想...
- Should i talk to Benjamin ? Because I'm sorry
你只是个给我送饭的
to think that you're just the person who brings me my food.
你愿意的话你可以和他谈谈
You can talk to him all you want,
但他不会告诉你任何东西
but he won't tell you anything.
- 你在帮他干活 - 不  我没在为他工作
- You work for him. - No, I don't work for him.
他是头儿
He's in charge.
我们不搞这一套  Jack
It doesn't work that way over here, Jack
- 我们一起做决定 - 真的吗?
We make decisions together. Really?
当我拿着那只破碗指着你脖子的时候
Because when I was holding that broken plate at your neck,
他看起来对你的死活根本无所谓
he seemed happy to just let you die.
我是说  这好像...
I mean, it felt like
他自己一个人做了一个决定
he made that decision on his own.
你不知道你自己在说什么
You don't know what you're talking about.
我没有服从他的决定
I don't answer to him.
Juliet  我需要你帮忙
Juliet, I need you.
等一下好吗?
Can it wait?
那家伙回来了  情况不太好
The sub is back. We have a situation,
马上和我来
so come with me now.
开始干活了
Time for work.
感觉有点无聊么  唐人街来的小子
Soundin' a little stuffy there, Chinatown.
想让鼻子开花吗?
Need to blow your nose?
- 给我个理由 - 我想我已经说过了
- Just give me an excuse. - Thought I just did.
我该做什么  问候你老妈?
What I gotta do, talk about your mother?
Danny  你在吗?
Danny, are you there?
是的
Yeah.
等等
Hold on.
好了  快走
Okay, go
什么?
What?
他们在哪?
- Where are they?
他们在...
- They're back in the...
都是你的错  Juliet
This is bad, Juliet.
抬稳点
Keep her steady.
她会好的  是吗?  她会没事吗?
She'll be okay?
发生了什么?
What happened?
我们的人干的
We happened.
什么?
What?
我在这里这么久早知道
I've been on this rock long enough to realize
他们这伙人是不会自相残杀的
they ain't in the business of shootin' each other.
是我们干的
We did it.
我们的人
Our team.
你在笑?
You smiling?
混蛋  好吧  我是在笑
Damn right I'm smiling.
因为我们可以开溜了
'Cause we just got our ticket outta here.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译： 小黄 后期：梁良 双语字幕：yuyiqi1983
你在干什么?
What are you doin'?
你要把我冲出去吗
安静点  我在考虑
Shush up. I'm thinking.
警告
Warning
奖品  奖品
Reward. Reward.
你知道那个担架上的女人吗?
You know that chick they brought in on a stretcher?
是那个鼻子破了的家伙的女朋友
That's broken nose man's girl.
他们叫他放哨的
They call him Pickett.
那么那个放哨的分散了他们的注意力
Well, Pickett is distracted at the moment.
所以呢?
So?
学着点  小姐
Watch and learn, little lady.
警告
Warning.
有条输送管在给这台机器输送果汁
There's juice pumpin' into this box from somewhere.
下次有人来拉我出去的话
Next time someone comes to pull me out,
我会等他踩进我的小泳池里
I'm gonna wait till they step in my little swimming hole,
然后抓住他们  滋的一声
then I grab 'em. Zap.
他们触电倒地后  我就可以拿到钥匙了
They fall back from the shock, I snag the keys.
我打赌熊是想不出这个主意的
Bet the bears never thought of that.
你们都会触电的
You're both gonna get electrocuted.
是的  但我被电过一次 我承受的了
Yeah, but I felt the jolt. I can take it.
另一个呢...他不会有准备的
The other guy, he ain't gonna be ready for it.
怎么  你认为我疯了?
What, you think I'm crazy?
不  事实上我很感兴趣
No, I'm actually impressed.
把你眼里的星光擦去吧  亲爱的
Well, wipe the stars out of your eyes, sweetheart
因为我们必须这么做
'cause we're gonna do this
那Jack怎么办?
What about him?
关他什么事?
我们不知道他是否在这
We don't even know if he's here.
甚至还不知道他是否活着
Hell, we don't even know if he's alive.
我们得照顾好我们自己
We gotta take care of us.
每个人都会有私心的  小妞
It's every man for himself, Freckles.
好了  Ford  够了
All right, Ford, that's enough.
所有人返回牢房
All inmates are required
立即执行...
to report to your cells for mandatory...
问题是我只在意你的手 而不是你的眼神
Problem is, I was following your hands, no your eyes.
问题是你又老又不说话
Problem is, you old and dumb.
你藏在那里了?
Where did you hide it?!
那个被打的是谁?
Who's the punching bag?
刚来  叫Munson
Just got here. Name is Munson.
听说他窃了政府一千万
Rumor has it he ripped off the government for 10 mil,
但政府却找不到这笔钱
but they never found the money.
- 真该死 - 说话啊  小子
I'll be damned.
如果你的监狱长朋友不制止的话
If your buddy the warden didn't keep breaking up the fights,
Munson马上就会变死人了
Munson would be a dead man.
那个狗娘养的
That son of a bitch.
你晚上在枕头上放薄荷了吗?
You get little mints on your pillow at night, too?
什么?
- Sorry?
你才这里都一周了就开始做手提包了?
- You been here, what, a week, and you're on tote bag duty?
我来了九个月了  还在倒垃圾
I've been here nine months. I'm still pushing trash.
什么意思?
Well, what does that mean?
你以为监狱长制止你们打架...
You think the warden's breakin' up those fights
是因为你很帅吗  伙计?
'cause you're cute, Costanza?
他是为了那一千万在演戏
He's makin' a play for that 10 mil.
首先  给你点好处
First step, butter you up.
给你个好工作
Give you a plum job.
然后  监狱长就会向你妻子动手
Step two, the warden will reach out to your wife,
让她和你作对
use her against you.
巧妙的计划
Textbook con.
那么你友善的告诉我这些
And you're telling me
是因为你想...
this out of the kindness
这建议是免费的  伙计
- The advice is free, Murgatroyd.
过去的九个月   那个监狱长让我生活生不如死
Past nine months, that warden's made my life a living hell.
他拿了好处  而你却什么也没有
He gets that 10 mil you ain't got,
我真想杀了自己
I just might have to kill myself.
您好  狱长
Well, howdy, warden.
他妨碍你了吗  Munson?
He bothering you, Munson?
什么风把你吹到裁缝店来了  老板?
So what brings you　to the sewing shop, Boss?
别以为我无权给你加刑  Ford
Don't think　I an't extend your stay, Ford.
只要一个电话就够了
All it takes is one call.
一个电话
One call.
把那个垃圾捡起来好吗?
How about you get that trash?
魔王出现了
oh, yeah. It's the big Kahuna.
吃过午饭了吗?
- Lunch already?
- 你体重多少? - 什么?
- What do you weigh?　- What?
你体重多少?
- What do you weigh?
180左右
180, give or take.
你几岁了?
- 32.
别骗我
- don't lie.
很好
Good.
再见吧你
Sayonara, sucke
你干了什么?
What did you do?
我们把它关了
We turned it off.
Sawyer
在天空变紫色后的两天里...
...two days since the sky turned purple,
我们瞎了  伙伴们都倒下了
we've been blind, our coms are all down
我没办法再支撑了
and I can't get 'em back up again,
为了避免你忘记Colleen的伤痕...
and in case you forgot,  - Colleen's in critical...
Juliet在照看她
- Juliet's taking care of her.
我在哪?
Where am I?
你们想干什么?
What the hell are you doin' to me?
放开我
Let me out!
Jason  放我出去
Jason. Let me out !
拜托咬紧它
Bite down on this, please.
你咬吧
You bite down on it.
会很痛的
It's for the pain.
什么?
What?!
等等
Wait!
放开我
Let me out now!
- 我讨厌针 - 不  不
I hate needles.
不  你们在干吗?
No! What are you doing?
你们干什么?
Hey! What are you doing?
不
你们到底在干什么?
What the hell are you doing?!
不对  你得穿透胸骨  是胸骨
No, you have to go through the sternum. Th sternum.
- 不 - 就像电影里的一样
- Like in the movies.
- 我知道 - 什么?
- I know, I know.
不  不
- 一... - 你干什么?
- One...- What are you doing?!
二...
Two...
等等
Wait!
顾自己玩吧  兄弟  我来拿根球杆
Don't mind me, brother. I'm just gonna take one of your clubs.
Hurley说没问题的
Hurley said it'd be all right.
Hurley  是吗?
Hurley, huh?
就是说你们又要去拯救大家了
Must mean you're off to save the day.
那么...我能拿一个吗?
So... I can take one of these?
拿5号杆吧
Take the 5-iron.
我从来不用
I never use it.
这样  当你们做你们的事
That way, when you die in the jungle
死在丛林里后
doing whatever you're doing,
我就不用去找它了
I don't have to go looking for it.
谢谢  伙计
Thanks, mate.
你知道  你应该...
You know, you might want
肩膀甩的范围更大些
to square your shoulders a bit more.
你会打高尔夫?
- You play golf?
我是苏格兰人  玩得开心
- I'm scottish.
这是什么?
What the hell?
快点
Hey, come on.
摇动吧  快点  快点  快点
Hey, move. Let's move. Hey, come on, come on, come on!
- 你在干什么? - 快点  快点  快  快
- What are you doing? - Come on. Come on,
开始吧  开始吧 开始吧  跳舞吧
Let's move it, let's move it.
- 开始吧  快 - 你在干嘛?
- 动起来  动起来  动起来 - 你有毛病?
What's your problem?
快  快  快  快
你弄死了它?
Did you just kill that bunny?
你知道起搏器吗?
You know what a pacemaker is?
- 什么? - 他们把起搏器放在...
What? They stick 'em in the tickers
做过搭桥手术的人的心脏里
of people who've had bypass work,
他们的心脏需要驱动力
a little jump, a kick start.
那只兔子就装了个小起搏器
The rabbit had a small pacemaker
它会在这些时候产生驱动力 像是太兴奋...
set to deliver its kick start, should it get too excited...
或是太焦虑...或是害怕...
or anxious or frightened...
或是企图逃走
or should it try to escape.
假如你对于你的年龄和体重
Assuming that you were telling the truth
没有说谎的话
about your age and weight,
你静止时的心率
your resting heart rate
应该在每分钟70下
should be about 70 beats per minute.
然而你活动时的心率
Your active heart rate, however,
可能会在140
that would be about 140.
超过这个数字  你的起搏器...
Which is the point at which your pacemaker...
就会弄爆你的心脏
will cause your heart to explode.
这样我就可以确信你会乖乖的了
Which is how I know that you're gonna start behaving now.
这只表可以监控你的脉搏
The watch monitors your pulse.
如果心跳接近危险区域15下以内的话
If you get within 15 beats of your danger zone,
它会响  一旦它响了
it'll start to beep. If and when it beeps,
你就得让自己冷静
you're gonna want to relax yourself.
做做深呼吸  瑜伽什么的
Do some deep breathing, some yoga.
如果你想我死
If you want me dead,
为什么不一枪了结了我?
why don't you just shoot me and get it over with?
因为我们不是杀手  James
Because we're not killers, James.
还有件事  Kate
Oh, and one other thing. - Kate.
你碰她的话  我发誓... - 如果你告诉她我们做了什么...
You touch her, I swear...
我们把什么植入你体内   我们在监控你们
what we put in you, that we're watching you,
你告诉她这些的话
you tell her any of these things,
我们也会给她装上一个的
we'll put one in her, too.
Sawyer?
Sawyer  你没事吧?
Sawyer, are you okay?
给你们擦身子用的
That's so you can clean yourselves up.
Kate  如果有不合身的话
And, Kate, if any of that doesn't fit,
叫我一声就好了  好吗?
you just give me a holler, okay?
发生了什么?
What happened?
他们做了什么?
What did they do to you?
没什么  就问了些问题
Nothing. They just asked me questions.
没什么大不了的
Ain't important.
告诉我  发生了什么?
Talk to me. What happened?
听着  我告诉过你  没事
Look, I told you, nothing happened.
别再问了
So quit asking me.
转过去
Turn around.
那是什么?
What's that?
我的手表  坏了的
Just my watch. It's busted.
- 你哪来的表? - 我不用每件事都向你汇报吧
- When did you get a watch? - Look, I don't tell you everything!
让我安静会儿  该死的
Just leave me alone, damn it.
穿上衣服
Put some clothes on.
你好  Sawyer.
Hello, Sawyer.
我叫James Ford  我想你知道的
It's James Ford, and I know you know that,
你告我的时候就用的这个名字
cause you got it right when you pressed charges.
你生我的气?
You're mad at me?
看看我的处境
Well, look where I am.
你想我怎么样?  你骗了我
What did you want me to do? You conned me.
你想要什么?
Something you want?
是的是的  是有东西
Yeah. Yeah. There is.
快点  我有执照的
Come on. I got license plates to make.
她是谁?
What's this?
是你女儿
This is your daughter.
你想怎么样?
What do you want?
首先我想让你知道这个
Well, first I wanted you to know.
然后呢?  你想我一看这张照片
Then what? Think I'm gonna take　one look at this picture
就去参加"老爸最好"这个节目吗?
and turn into "father knows best"?
我们住在新墨西哥州的这个小地方
We're living in this little place　in Albuquerque.
- 在一所大学附近... - 你和我说这些干嘛?
It's near the university.　- Why are you telling me this?
我只是...想让你给她写封信
-  just...　thought you could write her a letter.
她叫Clementine
Her name's Clementine.
我该死的可以写点什么?
What the hell am I gonna write?
"亲爱的变形金刚"? 她还是个孩子
"Dear goo-goo ga-ga"?
她不是我的
She's a baby. She ain't mine.
Sawyer  她...
Sawyer, she...
我没有女儿
I ain't got no daughter.
我查看过我的笼子了
I've been checking out my cage,
我想如果我爬上去的话
and I think if I climb to the top,
我可以从缝隙里挤出去
I can squeeze through those bars.
他们离这里很远
They're spaced farther apart up there.
别找事了
Don't bother.
你在说什么?
- What are you talking about?
我说放聪明点
- I'm talking about being smart.
我想我们还是乖乖呆着
I think we should just chill out here a while,
听天由命吧
get the lay of the land.
...在控制下了
...under control.
是吗?  你知道他怎么对Karl吗?
Yeah?　You know what he's doing to Karl?
你知道他怎么做吗?
You know what he's doing?
把他们两个带来是个错误
- 你们对Sawyer怎么了? - 没什么
- What did you do to Sawyer?　- Nothing.
- 我听到他在喊 - Jack
I heard him yelling,
- 你衣服上有血 - Jack
yo've got blood on your clothes.
- 你们对他怎么了? - 这不是他的血
What did you do to him?!　- It's not his blood.
那是谁的?
Then whose blood is it?
是一个快死了的女人的血
It's the bldod of a woman who's dying.
Jack  我...
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
是Jack
it's Jack!
- Jack - 医生
Jack  Jack
Jack
你疯了吗?  把他带来这里?
Have you lost your mind? - You bring him here?
他是个医生  他能帮上忙
- He's a doctor. He can help.
这不是理由...
- Well, this is not why...
你想她死吗?  来吧
- o you want her to die? Come on.
发生了什么?
- What happened?
腹部中枪
- Gunshot wound to the abdomen.
那些不是她的
Those aren't hers.
来吧
Come on.
- 他来干什么? - Danny  他是来帮忙的
- What's he doing in here? - Danny, he's here to help.
- 告诉他是谁干的  他应该知道 - Danny...
Tell him who did this. He ought to know that.
- 我要他离开这里 - Danny  出去  快
- I need him out of here. - anny, get out. Go.
- 拜托 - 不行  不行  她是我的妻子
- No way! She's my  wife!
Danny  他们会处理的
- Danny, they got it.
我把子弹取出了  但她还在流血
I got the bullet out, but she's still bleeding.
右上方在大出血
Right upper quadrant. Its flowing badly.
- 不不  我已经填上了 - 我要你夹住肝脏
- No, no, I padded it. - I need you to clamp under the liver
这样我就能看看背面了
so I can get a look back there.
我...我不是外科医生
I'm not a surgeon.
我知道  但我需要你这么做
I know, but I need you to do this.
这里
Here.
她腔静脉在出血
She's got a retrohepatic caval bleed.
在肝脏后面  难怪你没发现
It's, uh, behind the liver. That's why you missed it.
我要棉塞  越多越好
I need lap pads, as many as you've got.
好的  再来一个
All right. Another one.
电击器
A crash cart. Now.
- Juliet  我需要电击器 - 坏掉了
- Juliet, I need paddles. - It's broken.
我们没有...
We haven't had,
Jack  我们以前没遇到过这种事
Jack, we haven't had anything happen before.
我们没有...我们... 我没有...我没有...
We didn't-we- I don't...
一  二
三  四  五  六...
时间快...
Time of death is...
她死了
She's gone
他们干的  他们干的好事
Danny  等等  Danny  等等  等等
冷静点
Take it easy.
Take it easy!
- 别冲动 - 闭嘴
- Shut up!
你爱他吗?
You love this guy?
什么?
What?
- 我说  你爱他吗? - 住手
- I said, do you love him? - Stop!
你爱他吗?
- 你爱他吗? - 放开他
- Do you love him?! - Leave him alone!
你爱他吗?
- Do you love him?!
你干什么?  住手
- what are you doing? Stop!
你...爱...他...吗?
Do... you... love... him?
是的  是的  我爱他  我爱他
Yes, I love him! I love him.
我爱他  求你了
I love him. Please.
把他锁起来
Lock him up!
我要和你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
- 抱歉  我很忙 - 这很重要
Sorry, I'm busy. It's important.
拜托
Please.
你是对的  我爱她
You were right. I loved her.
我认为...我真的以为她...
And I thought... I really thought she...
一千万  很多绿钞啊  伙计
10 mil's a lot of greenbacks, killer.
可以改变一切
Tends to change things.
这就是为什么她没联系过你
That's why you never get attached,
因为你一旦你在意了
'cause once you care,
就是你被抓的时候了
that's when they can come at you.
那你的那位想要什么?
Well, what did yours want?
我看见...那天我看见你和...
I saw you the other day with...
一个女人一起  她想要什么?
with a woman. What did she want?
我没有的东西
Somethin' I ain't got.
就这样吧  你自己哭一场吧
That all? You had yourself a good cry.
介意我回去看看George得到他的农场了吗?
Mind if I go back and see if George gets his farm?
我要你转移掉...把钱转移掉
I need you to move it... the money.
你没偷的那笔钱?
The money you didn't steal?
你我都知道我偷了
We both know I did.
Lila请了个私家侦探 找到是迟早的事
Lila's hired a P.I. She's gonna find it.
就算帮帮我  你必须这么做
Do this for me. You have to.
不
太危险了  我不做活靶子
It's too dangerous. I'll be a walking target.
如果你不帮我   监狱长就会得到所有的钱
If you don't help me, the Warden'll get it all.
他会是赢家
He'll win.
求你了  求你了
Please.
你还好吧?
Are you okay?
很好
那家伙打起来就像女人
Guy hits like a girl.
一点攻击性都没有
No offense.
他为什么那么干?
Why did he do that?
我怎么知道
Hell if I know.
这些人什么时候告诉过我们为什么?
These people ever make any sense to you?
你干什么?
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
看不出来吗?
- what does it look like?
等一下  小妞
Hang on a second,  freckles.
我告诉过你  这不是时候
I told you the time ain't right.
我们得逃走  这也是你说的
You're the one that said we had to go.
- 那是以前... - 在什么以前?
- Well, that was before... - Before what?
我不知道他们对你做了什么
I don't know what they did to you,
但是我知道你害怕得不敢讲实话了
but I know you're scared enough to lie about it,
那比任何他们的所作所为
and that scares me more than anything
- 都让我感到害怕 - 等等
that they have done to us before.
等等
Wait.
- 你在干什么? - 把你弄出来
- What are you doing? - Getting you out of here.
- 不要 - 我不会撇下你的  Sawyer
- Don't. - I'm not leaving you, Sawyer.
- 我可以打开它 - 你已经出来了  你得走了
- I can get it open. - You're already out. You gotta go.
- 别管我了 - 什么?
You gotta leave me! - What?
- 快跑 - 他们对你怎么了?
- What did they do to you?
你快走
- You go!
那是什么?
What is that thing?
快走  每个人都有私心...
- It's every man for himself.
你为什么不回击?
- Why didn't you fight back?!
快跟我讲实话 哪怕你这辈子就说这么一次
Tell me the truth for once in your life!
如果你真的爱我...
If you really love me...
就快走
Go.
我这么说只是为了让他不要打你
I only said that so he'd stop hitting you.
快走
Run.
快
Hurry!
你干什么?
What the hell are you doing?
Kate
别傻了小妞  每个人都有私心
Damnit, Frackles, don't ! Every man for itself !
一起生  单独死
Live together, die alone.
你知道Danny想杀了他
You know Danny wants to kill him.
Danny可以等
Danny can wait.
要我把Shephard带回来吗?
Should I bring Shephard back?
不
我要让他再陪她坐一会儿
I want him to sit with her for a while longer.
我很抱歉  他们...他们得...
I'm sorry that they...
铐住你
they had to put handcuffs on you.
我是...
我是妇产科医生
I'm a fertility doctor.
我不习惯看到死亡
I'm not used to death.
她叫什么名字?
What was her name?
Col  Colleen的简称
Col. Short for Colleen.
我不应该...
I shouldn't-have,
我该早点来找你的
I should've come to get you sooner.
那也不会改变什么
It wouldn't have mattered.
你已经尽力了
There wasn't any more that you could have done.
她...在你把她放上手术台前
She was... She was dead
就已经没救了
before you put her on the table.
你这么说是为了让我好过点吗?
Are you... are you just saying that to make me feel better?
我不...
I don't...
我可不管你好不好过
I don't care about making you feel better.
我现在要把你带回去  我...
I'm gonna take you back now.
很抱歉把你带来这里
I'm sorry for bringing you here.
外面的X光片是谁的?
Whose x-rays are those, outside?
那些是脊椎骨的X光片
Those are spinal x-rays, and they belong
是一个大约40岁的男人的
to a man about 40 years old.
不管他是谁
And whoever he is,
在他1到4节椎骨上有一个巨大的瘤
he has a very large tumor on his I-4 vertebrae.
而我正好是一个脊椎外科医生
And I just happen to be a spinal surgeon.
所以告诉我  Juliet
So you tell me, Juliet,
我来这里是为了救谁?
who am I here to save?
那是...
Is that...
艺术品吗?
art?
不  只是一个实验
No, just an experiment.
好的
你要水果沙拉吗?
Do you want some fruit salad?
谢谢  我不饿
- Thanks. I'm not hungry.
你最好再等一会儿
You might want to wait a minute.
为什么?
Why's that?
早上好
Good morning.
我们去散散步吧
Let's go for a walk.
我得承认  Ford
I have to be honest, Ford.
当他们刚把你带来时
When they first brought you here,
我以为你只是个哑吧土鳖
I thought you were nothing more than a dumb hick.
现在我了解你了
Now I know better.
你是个知道怎么偷东西的哑吧土鳖
You're a dumb hick that knows how to steal.
我们快点了结了吧
Can we just get this over with?
好吧
Yeah, let's.
你还记得财政部的特工Freeman吗?
You remember agent Freedman from the treasury department?
那么  该你说了吧?
So, what do you got?
那一千万美元在一辆野马车里
The $10 million's in a red Bronco parked
车停在411公路旁23-C号
in a store-it-quick facility in Sawgrass,
23-C号
right off 441.
的一个便利店旁
Unit 23-C.
你的钱就在那
That's where your money is.
我们说好的
As agreed,
一旦那辆车找到了
the last six years of your sentence
钱也被追回了
have been commuted.
你后面六年的刑期
As soon as the truck is recovered
将会被减免
and the funds confirmed,
你的委托也将会被受理
yor commission will be processed.
现在你觉得怎么样?
Now how would you like that?
我想开一个新帐户  随便什么银行
I wanna set up a new account, don't matter what bank.
只要在新墨西哥州就可以了
Just make it in Albuquerque.
好的
用Clementine Phillips这个名字开户
Put it in the name of Clementine Phillips.
好的  Clementine Phillips
Okay. Clementine Phillips.
我这么做是因为
And I want it so there's no way
她永远也不会知道钱是哪里来的了
she can ever find out where the money's from.
谁是Clementine Phillips?
Who's Clementine Phillips?
我们两清了吧?
We done?
恭喜你  Ford
Congratulations, Ford.
你连哄带骗的离开了监狱
You just lied and cheated your way out of prison.
你自由了
You're a free man.
不远了  James
Not much further, James.
下个山峰的顶端就是了
Just to the top of the next rise.
那里有什么?
What's up there?
我想让你看的东西
Something I want you to see.
"那就是你经常向往的地方吗  George?"
"Is it that little place you've always wanted, George?"
什么?
What
怎么  你不看书吗?
don't you read?
是里的
It's from "of mice and men."
你会喜欢的
You'd like it.
那条小狗被杀了
Puppies get killed.
你带我来这是想杀我?
You bring me up here to kill me?
让那个你放在我身体里的东西
Make that thing you put inside me
炸了我的心脏?
blow up my damn heart?
你的心脏不会爆炸的  James
Your heart's not gonna blow up, James.
我们只是放进了一样东西  疑心
we put inside you was doubt.
那只表只是个心率监控器
Oh, the watch is a heart rate monitor,
没有其他作用了
but nothing more.
看看
Look.
我们给它的只是镇静剂  不是起搏器
We gave him a sedative, not a pacemaker.
我怎么知道是同一知兔子?
How do I know that's the same bunny?
你也可以在另外一只上也画个"8"
That you didn't just paint an"8" on another one?
随你怎么想
You don't.
你这个狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
我想给你看的不是这只兔子
The rabbit wasn't the thing I wanted to show you.
什么...
What the...
你去过Alcatraz吗?
You ever been to Alcatraz?
旅游的时候?
Take the tour?
现在你站的小岛上
Right now you're standing on a small island roughly
面积差不多是Alcatraz的两倍
twice the size of alcatraz.
而那边那个
And that over there,
是你们的岛
that's your island,
一个你们了解和喜爱的地方
the one you've come to know and love.
我只是想让你知道
i just wanted you to know,
你无处可逃
there's nowhere to run.
你做这些只是...
You did all this just to...
只是为了把我关在一个破笼子里?
Just to keep me in a damn cage?
我们这么做是因为唯一可以赢得
We did all this because the only way
骗子的尊重的方法就是去欺骗他们
to gain a con man's respect is to con him.
你很不错  "Sawyer"
You're pretty good, "Sawyer."
但我们更出色
We're a lot better.
有意思的是  让你规规矩矩的
Funny thing is, us telling you
不是因为起搏器
about the pacemaker
而是因为我威胁会伤害她
wasn't what kept you in line. It was when i threatened her.
你是这么努力得让她觉得 你不在乎她
You work so hard to make her think you don't care,
和你不需要她  但是...
that you don't need her, but...
"一个人爱上了另一个人就会疯狂
"A guy goes nuts if he ain't got nobody."
"不管这人是谁
"It don't make no difference who the guy is,
只要是和你在一起的"
as long as he's with you."
"我告诉你...
"I tell you...
"我告诉你如果一个人太孤单的话
"I tell you a guy gets too lonely
就会感到不适"
and he gets sick."
你到底在说什么?
- What the hell are you talking about?
是"人鼠之间"里的
- It's from "of mice and men."
你不看书吗?
Don't you read?
走吧
Come on.
回你的笼子去吧
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■